Guide to the William E. Irwin Photograph Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Texas, circa 1893-1940; Series IX; 1.25; (1 box)
  - Unidentified Locations in Texas
    - View of a man, identified as William Edward "Ed" Irwin, field dressing the carcass of a deer with a knife in Texas, circa 1893-1903; 1 mounted photographic print (Box 10, Folder 780)
      Inscription on recto of mount: "Deer hunting in west Tex."
    - View of a man, identified as William Edward "Ed" Irwin, walking with his back to the camera and carrying a rifle toward a horse with three deer carcasses on the ground, probably in Texas, circa 1893-1903; 1 mounted photographic print (Box 10, Folder 781)
      Inscription on recto of mount: "Starting for camps"
    - Exterior portrait of a man, identified as William Edward "Ed" Irwin, posed standing and holding a rifle by a deer carcass on the ground, probably in Texas, circa 1893-1903; 1 mounted photographic print (Box 10, Folder 782)
    - Exterior portrait of two boys posed with a tied-down cow in a yard in Texas, circa 1893-1903; 1 mounted photographic print (Box 10, Folder 783)
      Inscription on recto of mount: "Branding cattle in Southern, Tex."
    - Exterior portrait of a man with a lariat posed standing over a tied-down cow, which is also tied to a horse, in western Texas, circa 1893-1903; 1 mounted photographic print and 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 10, Folder 784)
      Inscription on recto of mount: "Views in West Tex."
    - View of women and men chiefly posed sitting in eight horse-drawn wagons, probably in Texas, circa 1893-1903; 1 mounted photographic print (Box 10, Folder 785)
    - Exterior portrait of eight men posed standing and six holding rifles in a camp with three covered wagons, identified as Tom Johnson, John Cot, S. Jack Mankins, Tom Martin, Jim Martin, Vestus Horton, General Martin, and William Edward "Ed" Irwin, probably in Texas, circa 1895-1903; 1 mounted photographic print (Box 10, Folder 786)
    - View of a hunting camp with tents, wagons, and eleven men, as well as five deer carcasses and many fowl carcasses hung from a line, probably in Texas, circa 1893-1903; 2 unmounted photographic prints (Box 10, Folder 787)
    - View of five deer carcasses hanging from a line with five rifles in a hunting camp, probably in Texas, 1928; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 10, Folder 788)
      Inscription on verso of print: "Bear Creek, 1928"
    - View of two American bison grazing, probably in Texas, circa 1893-1903; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 10, Folder 789)
    - View of two American bison grazing, probably in Texas, circa 1893-1903; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 10, Folder 790)
    - Exterior portrait of a dog with his paw on the face of a deer carcass, probably in Texas, circa 1893-1903; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 10, Folder 791)
      Inscription in negative: "A Faithful Pal, Photo by Ed Irwin"
      Inscription on verso: "By Ed Irwin, 1702 E. 1st St., Tucson, Ariz., Picture #19"
    - Interior view of a soda fountain, probably in Texas, circa 1893-1903; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 10, Folder 792)
    - View of a valley with houses, probably in Texas, circa 1893-1903; 3 unmounted photographic prints (Box 10, Folder 793)
    - View of a three-story building, probably in Texas, 1940; 3 unmounted photographic prints (Box 10, Folder 794)
- Yellowstone National Park, circa 1895-1905; Series X; 0.42; (1 box)
  Series X is organized into six subseries: Gardner River, Mammoth Hot Springs, Tower Creek, Upper Geyser Basin, Yellowstone River, and Unidentified Locations in Yellowstone National Park
  This series chiefly consists of landscape views of Yellowstone National Park, including geothermal features, rivers, waterfalls
  - Gardner River
    - View of an antelope herd feeding near the Gardner River, probably in Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, circa 1895-1905; 3 unmounted photographic prints (Box 11, Folder 795)
      Inscription in negative of a print: "Antelop feeding along Gardner Riv. Wyoming"
      Inscription on verso of a print: "Antelope feeding in Yellowstone National Park"
      Inscription on verso of a print: "Antelope feeding along the Gardner River, Wyoming"
  - Mammoth Hot Springs
    - View of a sulphur terrace at Mammoth Hot Springs, Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, circa 1895-1905; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 11, Folder 796)
      Inscription in negative: "Sulphur terrace, Yellowstone National Park, Photo by Ed Irwin"
    - View of a sulphur terrace at Mammoth Hot Springs, Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, circa 1895-1905; 1 mounted hand colored photographic print and 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 11, Folder 797)
      Inscription in negative of the unmounted print: "Sulphur terrace, Yellow Stone Park, Photo by Ed Irwin"
      Inscription on recto of the mounted print: "Views around Ft. Yellowstone, Wyoming"
    - View of a sulphur terrace at Mammoth Hot Springs, Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, circa 1895-1905; 1 mounted hand colored photographic print and 4 unmounted photographic prints (Box 11, Folder 798)
      Inscription in negative of the unmounted prints: "Pulpit Terrace, Yellow Stone National Park, Photo by Ed Irwin"
      Inscription on recto of the mounted print: "Minerva Terrace, Yellow Stone National Park"
    - View of a sulphur terrace at Mammoth Hot Springs, Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, circa 1895-1905; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 11, Folder 799)
      Inscription in negative of print: "Terraces formed by hot sulpher water around Ft. Yellow Stone, Wyoming, Photo by Ed Irwin"
      Inscription on verso of print: "By Ed Irwin, 1702 E. 1st St., Tucson, Ariz., Picture #4"
    - View of a sulphur terrace at Mammoth Hot Springs, Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, circa 1895-1905; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 11, Folder 800)
    - View of a sulphur terrace at Mammoth Hot Springs, Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, circa 1895-1905; 1 hand colored mounted photographic print (Box 11, Folder 801)
      Inscription on recto of print: "Pulpit Terrace, Yellow Stone National Park"
    - View of Angel Terrace at Mammoth Hot Springs, Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, circa 1895-1905; 1 hand colored mounted photographic print (Box 11, Folder 802)
      Inscription on recto of print: "Angel Terrace, Yellow Stone National Park"
  - Tower Creek
    - View of Tower Fall, a waterfall on Tower Creek, Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, circa 1895-1905; 1 mounted photographic print and 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 11, Folder 803)
      Inscription in negative of the unmounted print: "Tower Falls, Yellowstone Park, Photo by Ed Irwin"
      Inscription on recto of the mounted print: "Tower Falls, Yellowstone Park"
  - Upper Geyser Basin
    - View of Kepler Cascades on the Firehole River in the Upper Geyser Basin, Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, circa 1895-1905; 1 mounted photographic print and 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 11, Folder 804)
      Inscription on recto of the mounted print: "Cascade Falls, Yellowstone National Park"
      Inscription in negative of the unmounted print: "Cascade Falls, Yellowstone National Park, Photo by Ed Irwin"
    - View of Old Faithful Geyser as it erupts in the Upper Geyser Basin, Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, with a woman, a boy, and two men also in the image, circa 1895-1905; 1 mounted hand colored photographic print and 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 11, Folder 805)
      Inscription in negative of the unmounted print: "Old Faithful Geyser, Yellowstone National Park, Photo by Ed Irwin"
      Inscription on recto of the mounted print: "Old Faithful Geyser, Yellow Stone National Park"
    - View of Punch Bowl Spring in Upper Geyser Basin, Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, circa 1895-1905; 1 mounted hand colored photographic print and 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 11, Folder 806)
      Inscription on recto of the mounted print: "Punch Bowl Geyser, Yellow Stone National Park"
      Inscription in negative of the unmounted print: "Punch Bowl Geyser, Yellowstone National Park, Photo by Ed Irwin"
    - View of the Firehole River at Upper Geyser Basin in Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, circa 1895-1905; 1 mounted hand colored photographic print and 2 unmounted photographic prints (Box 11, Folder 807)
      Inscription on recto of the mounted print: "Views along the Fire Hole River, Yellow Stone National Park"
      Inscription in negative of the unmounted prints: "Along the Fire Hole Riv., Yellowstone National Park, Photo by Ed Irwin"
    - View of Riverside Geyser in the Upper Geyser Basin of Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, circa 1895-1905; 1 hand colored mounted photographic print (Box 11, Folder 808)
      Inscription on recto of the mounted print: "River Side Geyser, Yellow Stone Park"
    - View of the Firehole River at Firehole Falls in Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, circa 1895-1905; 1 hand colored mounted photographic print (Box 11, Folder 809)
      Inscription on recto of print: "Views along the Fire Hole River, Yellow Stone National Park"
    - View of Grotto Geyser in the Upper Geyser Basin, Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, circa 1895-1905; 1 hand colored mounted photographic print (Box 11, Folder 810)
      Inscription on recto of print: "Geysers in Yellow Stone National Park"
    - View of Grotto Geyser in the Upper Geyser Basin, Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, circa 1895-1905; 1 hand colored mounted photographic print (Box 11, Folder 811)
      Inscription on recto of print: "Grotto Geysers, Yellow Stone National Park"
  - Yellowstone River
    - View of Upper Falls of Yellowstone River with rock formations, Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, circa 1895-1905; 2 unmounted photographic prints (Box 11, Folder 812)
      Inscription in negative of the unmounted print: "Upper Falls on the Yellow Stone Riv., Wyoming, Photo by Ed Irwin"
    - View of a herd of American bison in the foothills along the Yellowstone River, probably in Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, circa 1895-1905; 1 mounted photographic print and 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 11, Folder 813)
      Inscription on recto of the mounted print: "Buffalo feeding in the foot hills along the Yellow Stone Riv., Wyo."
      Inscription in negative of the unmounted print: "Buffalo feeding in the foot hills along the Yellow Stone Riv., Wyoming, Photo by Ed Irwin"
    - View of Upper Falls of Yellowstone River with rock formations, Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, circa 1895-1905; 1 hand colored mounted photographic print (Box 11, Folder 814)
      Inscription on recto of the mounted print: "Upper Falls on the Yellow Stone Riv., Wyo."
  - Unidentified Locations in Yellowstone National Park
    - View of a deer by a frozen waterfall, probably in Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, circa 1895-1905; 2 unmounted photographic prints (Box 11, Folder 815)
    - View of a man and a woman mounted on horses with four additional pack horses in Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, circa 1895-1905; 1 mounted photographic print and 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 11, Folder 816)
      Inscription on recto of the mounted print: "Touring Yellow Stone Park with a pack outfit"
- Irwin Family, 1885-circa 1930; Series XI; 0.21; (1 box)
  Series XI is organized alphabetically by individuals and then couples, followed by groups and ephemera
  This series chiefly consists of portraits of Irwin family members, as well as a small group of ephemera
  - Bock, Era F.
    - Studio portrait of Era F. Bock, circa 1930; 1 photographic print in a protective cover (Box 12, Folder 817)
      Inscription on negative: "Boyd-Healer, Waco"
      Inscription on mount: "Era Bock, Waco, Texas"
  - Irwin, Carrie Matilda "Tillie" Allen
    - Studio portrait of Carrie Matilda "Tillie" Allen Irwin posed standing behind a chair, pinning something to her dress, circa 1900; 1 mounted photographic print (Box 12, Folder 818)
      Inscription on verso: "Mrs. W. E. Irwin"
    - Studio portrait of Carrie Matilda "Tillie" Allen Irwin posed standing behind a chair, wearing a suit and hat, and holding a cigar, circa 1900; 1 mounted photographic print (Box 12, Folder 819)
      Printed on recto: "Irwin, Chickasha, Ind. Ter."
      Inscription on recto: "Tillie"
    - Studio portrait of Carrie Matilda "Tillie" Allen Irwin posed standing with a camera, wearing a dress covered in photographs, circa 1900; 1 mounted photographic print (Box 12, Folder 820)
      Inscription on verso: "Tillie Irwin"
    - Studio portrait of Carrie Matilda "Tillie" Allen Irwin posed standing with one foot on a chair, wearing a suit and holding a hat in one hand, circa 1900; 1 mounted photographic print (Box 12, Folder 821)
      Printed on recto: "Irwin, Chickasha, I.T."
      Inscription on verso: "Tillie"
  - Irwin, Ethel Allison
    Ethel Allison Irwin (later Fahnestock) (1901-1995) was a daughter of John Allison Irwin and Mary Eileen Brady Irwin (1875-1966)
    - Studio portrait of a girl posed standing with roses in a basket, probably Ethel Allison Irwin, circa 1904; 1 mounted photographic print (Box 12, Folder 822)
      Embossed stamp on recto: "Irwin, Bisbee, Arizona"
      Inscription on verso: "Ethel"
  - Irwin, John Allison
    - Studio portrait of a man, identified as possibly John Allison Irwin, posed standing with his arm resting on a chair., circa 1904; 1 cabinet photograph (Box 12, Folder 823)
      Printed on recto: "Irwin & Mankins, Bellville, Texas"
  - Irwin, Grace N.
    Grace N. Irwin (born 1886) was the wife of Marvin Elmore Irwin
    - Studio portrait of Grace N. Irwin, posed standing and wearing a suit and hat, holding a small handbag, circa 1910; 1 mounted photographic print in a studio folder (Box 12, Folder 824)
      Includes a note by Marvin Elmore Irwin that describes her
  - Irwin, Marvin Elmore
    - Exterior portrait of Marvin Elmore Irwin reclining under a tree with a horse standing nearby, circa 1895; 1 mounted photographic print (Box 12, Folder 825)
      Ink stamp on mount: "Irwin & Mankins, Chickasha and Duncan, Ind. Ter."
    - Exterior portrait of Marvin Elmore Irwin posed standing in the crook of a tree, circa 1897; 1 mounted photographic print (Box 12, Folder 826)
      Ink stamp on mount: "Irwin & Mankins, Chickasha, Ind. Ter."
    - Exterior portrait of Marvin Elmore Irwin standing against a tree, wearing a printed woman's dress, circa 1897; 1 mounted photographic print (Box 12, Folder 827)
    - Studio portrait of Marvin Elmore Irwin, posed sitting with one arm resting on a table, holding a newspaper, and wearing a suit and top hat, circa 1900; 1 mounted photographic print (Box 12, Folder 828)
      Ink stamp on mount: "Irwin, Chickasha, Ind. Ter."
    - Studio portrait of Marvin Elmore Irwin, posed sitting on a low chair covered with furs, sorting through a trunk of letters, wearing a suit and hat, circa 1900; 2 mounted photographic prints (Box 12, Folder 829)
    - Exterior portrait of Marvin Elmore Irwin, posed standing, holding the reins of a white horse, wearing a hat and glasses, circa 1910; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 12, Folder 830)
    - Exterior portrait of Marvin Elmore Irwin, posed standing next to an automobile, wearing glasses and suspenders, circa 1910; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 12, Folder 831)
    - Studio bust portrait of Marvin Elmore Irwin, wearing a suit and glasses, circa 1915; 2 mounted photographic prints in studio folders (Box 12, Folder 832)
    - Studio bust portrait of Marvin Elmore Irwin, wearing a suit and glasses, circa 1915; 2 mounted photographic prints in studio folders (Box 12, Folder 833)
      Stamp on mount: "Carson's Studio, Douglas, Ariz."
    - Studio portrait of Marvin Elmore Irwin, posed sitting, wearing a suit and glasses, with his hands clasped around one knee, circa 1915; 1 mounted photographic print in a studio folder (Box 12, Folder 834)
    - Studio bust portrait of Marvin Elmore Irwin, wearing a suit and glasses, circa 1915; 1 mounted photographic print in a studio folder (Box 12, Folder 835)
    - Exterior portrait of Marvin Elmore Irwin, standing with an unidentified man, holding a camera, with people and a building in the background, circa 1920; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 12, Folder 836)
      Inscription on recto: "Two Goodlookers"
  - Irwin, William Edward "Ed"
    - Studio portrait of William Edward "Ed" Irwin, posed standing with one arm resting on a camera on a tripod, wearing a suit and bow tie, circa 1895; 1 cabinet photograph (Box 12, Folder 837)
    - Studio bust portrait of William Edward "Ed" Irwin posed wearing a suit and bow tie, circa 1900; 1 mounted photographic print (Box 12, Folder 838)
      Inscription on verso: "W. E. Irwin"
    - Studio portrait of William Edward "Ed" Irwin, posed sitting in a chair, wearing a suit and bow tie, with his legs crossed, circa 1900; 1 mounted photographic print (Box 12, Folder 839)
      Inscription on verso: "628 South 5th St. W. E. Irwin"
    - Collage of studio bust portraits of William Edward "Ed" Irwin, wearing a suit and tie, circa 1900; 1 cabinet photograph and 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 12, Folder 840)
      Ink stamp on recto of mount: "Irwin & Mankins, Photographers and View Artists"
      Inscription on verso of mount: "Cracker Jack"
      Inscription on verso: "W E Irwin"
    - Exterior portrait of a man, identified as William Edward "Ed" Irwin, holding a lariat and posed standing over a tied-down cow, which is also tied to a horse, circa 1900; 1 mounted photographic print (Box 12, Folder 841)
      Inscription on recto: "Irwin, Chickasha, Ind. Ter."
    - Exterior portrait of a man, identified as William Edward "Ed" Irwin, posed standing over a deer carcass and holding a rifle and the carcass of a wild turkey, circa 1900; 1 mounted photographic print (Box 12, Folder 842)
    - Studio bust portrait of William Edward "Ed" Irwin with a lapel pin with a masonic emblem, circa 1910; 1 mounted photographic print
      Stored in: Oversize, Box 14, folder 929
    - Studio portrait of William Edward "Ed" Irwin, posed sitting backwards in a chair, wearing a suit and bow tie, circa 1915; 1 mounted photographic print in a studio folder (Box 12, Folder 843)
      Ink stamp on recto of mount: "Carson Studio, Bisbee, Ariz."
    - Studio bust portrait of William Edward "Ed" Irwin, wearing a suit and bow tie, circa 1915; 1 mounted photographic print in a studio folder (Box 12, Folder 844)
    - Exterior portrait of William Edward "Ed" Irwin, wearing a suit and hat, posed sitting on a rock with two puma carcasses, circa 1920; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 12, Folder 845)
  - Sawyers, Minnie Pearl Irwin Bock Mitchell
    - Studio portrait of Minnie Pearl Irwin Bock Mitchell Sawyers, posed standing with one foot on the rung of a chair, with her hands in her pockets, wearing a suit and hat, circa 1895-1900; 1 mounted photographic print (Box 12, Folder 846)
      Inscription on verso: "Minnie Pearl Irwin"
    - Exterior portrait of Minnie Pearl Irwin Bock Mitchell Sawyers, posed sitting in front of a tree, holding a guitar, circa 1903; 1 mounted photographic print, hand colored (Box 12, Folder 847)
  - Irwin, Carrie Matilda "Tillie" Allen, and Marvin Elmore Irwin
    - Studio portrait of a woman and man, identified as Carrie Matilda "Tillie" Allen Irwin and Marvin Elmore Irwin, posed sitting; she wears a suit and hat and holds a guitar, and he wears a woman's dress, glasses, and feathered hat, circa 1900; 1 mounted photographic print (Box 12, Folder 848)
      Inscription on verso: "Tillie and Minnie [Marvin]"
    - Studio portrait of a woman and man, identified as Carrie Matilda "Tillie" Allen Irwin and Marvin Elmore Irwin, posed sitting and wearing hats; he holds a fan that partially obscures their faces, circa 1900; 1 mounted photographic print (Box 12, Folder 849)
  - Irwin, Carrie Matilda "Tillie" Allen, and William Edward "Ed" Irwin
    - Exterior portrait of William Edward "Ed" Irwin and Carrie Matilda "Tillie" Allen Irwin, both posed standing and wearing hats; he also holds a camera tripod in one hand, circa 1920; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 12, Folder 850)
    - Photocollage of portraits of William Edward "Ed" Irwin, and Carrie Matilda "Tillie" Allen Irwin, as well as an unidentified man, with a drawing of cave people with big cats, circa 1920; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 12, Folder 851)
      Inscription on verso: "Tiger - Thank heaven, stripes are out!"
  - Irwin, Marvin Elmore, and Grace N. Irwin
    - Exterior bust portrait of Marvin Elmore Irwin and Grace Irwin in a desert landscape and both wearing hats, circa 1920; 1 photographic postcard (Box 12, Folder 852)
  - Irwin, Marvin Elmore, and S. Jack Mankins
    - Studio portrait of S. Jack Mankins and Marvin Elmore Irwin posed kneeling and sitting, as well as gambling with dice and currency, circa 1900; 1 mounted photographic print (Box 12, Folder 853)
      Printed on recto: Irwin, Chickasha, Ind. Ter.
  - Irwin, William Edward, and Marvin Elmore Irwin
    - Studio portrait of William Edward "Ed" Irwin and Marvin Elmore Irwin posed sitting and eating watermelons, circa 1900; 1 mounted photographic print (Box 12, Folder 854)
      Inscription on verso: "W. E. and M. E. Irwin, watter time"
    - Exterior portrait of William Edward "Ed" Irwin and Marvin Elmore Irwin, posed standing and both wearing hats with a liquor bottle, circa 1920-1930; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 12, Folder 855)
      Ink stamp on verso: "A14"
  - Irwin, William Edward, and S. Jack Mankins
    - Studio portrait of William Edward "Ed" Irwin and S. Jack Mankins posed sitting and eating watermelons, both wearing hats, circa 1895-1903; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 12, Folder 856)
      Inscription on verso: "Ed and Jack in the watter time"
    - Studio portrait of William Edward "Ed" Irwin and S. Jack Mankins posed sitting and eating watermelons, Mankins also holds a revolver and Irwin reaches for a rifle, circa 1895-1903; 1 cabinet photograph (Box 12, Folder 857)
      Inscription on verso: "J. Mankins and Ed Irwin in watter melon time"
  - Irwin Family Groups
    - Studio portrait of four women, posed sitting, working on needlecraft, all wearing bonnets, including Minnie Pearl Irwin Bock Mitchell Sawyers, circa 1895; 1 cabinet photograph (Box 12, Folder 858)
      Printed on recto: "Irwin & Mankins, Duncan, I.T."
      Inscription on verso: "Minnie Pearl Irwin, center"
    - Studio portrait of four women, posed sitting around a table, smoking pipes, all wearing bonnets, including Minnie Pearl Irwin Bock Mitchell Sawyers, circa 1895; 1 cabinet photograph (Box 12, Folder 859)
    - Exterior portrait of William Edward "Ed" Irwin and two women, identified as Minnie Pearl Irwin and Lou Irwin, all posed sitting near a tree, circa 1900; 1 cabinet photograph (Box 12, Folder 860)
      Ink stamp on recto of mount: "Irwin & Mankins, Chickasha and Duncan, Indian Ter."
      Inscription on verso: "Minnie Ed and Lou Irwin"
    - Studio portrait of three men posed standing, identified as John Allison Irwin, William Edward "Ed" Irwin, and Marvin Elmore Irwin, circa 1900; 1 mounted photographic print (Box 12, Folder 861)
    - Exterior portrait of four men posed standing along a wire fence in front of a wooden building; identified as William Edward "Ed" Irwin at the extreme left, and Marvin Elmore Irwin second from the right, circa 1910; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 12, Folder 862)
    - Studio portrait of two men posed standing, as well as a woman and man posed sitting, identified as the Irwin family, circa 1910; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 12, Folder 863)
      Identified from left to right, posed standing, John Allison Irwin and William Edward "Ed" Irwin; posed sitting, Mary Frances Elmore Irwin and Marvin Elmore Irwin